You have to climb Mount Kusama
عليك أن تتسلق جبل كوساما
and you must do a ritual.
ويجب عليك القيام بطقوس.
- But you need a date. - For your dad?
- لكنك بحاجة إلى تاريخ. - لوالدك؟
Does your mom know about that?
هل تعلم والدتك بذلك؟
Not for my dad! A date for you!
ليس لأبي! موعد لك!
Look! I don't need your help!
انظر! لا أحتاج مساعدتك!
You are the most useless family member!
أنت الأكثر عديمة الفائدة فرد من العائلة!
Is there... a private tour available?
هل هناك... جولة خاصة متاحة؟
- Sir Justin's does that. - He said Sir Justin.
- السير جوستين يفعل ذلك. - قال السير جاستن .
- Miss Cheska. - Oh?
- الآنسة تشيسكا. - أوه؟
- She'll come with you, too. - You're coming too, right?
- سوف تأتي معك أيضًا. - أنت قادم أيضاً، أليس كذلك؟
- Oh, I'd love to. - Welcome to Hotel 88.
- أوه، أود أن. - مرحبا بكم في فندق 88.
The hotel that will force you to participate.
الفندق الذي سيفعل ذلك يجبرك على المشاركة.
You said you saw a folder when Uncle Mike left.
قلت أنك رأيت مجلد عندما غادر العم مايك.
Ah, yes. I just mentioned it to Sir Henry recently.
آه، نعم. لقد ذكرت للتو إلى السير هنري مؤخرًا.
But do you know what's in it? Or who's it from?
ولكن هل تعرف ما هو في ذلك؟ أو من هو؟
The courier just gave it, but I'm sure it's Sir Mike's.
أعطاها الساعي للتو، لكنني متأكد من أنه السير مايك.
- [SCREAMS] Ahh! - What happened?
- [صرخات] آه! - ماذا حدث؟
- What's that smell? - That odor needs
- ما هذه الرائحة؟ - تلك الرائحة تحتاج
to be eliminated by tonight.
ليتم القضاء عليها بحلول هذه الليلة.
- Fine, I'll do it. - [CLATTERS]
- حسنًا، سأفعل ذلك. - [طقطقة]
[SCREAMS] Ah!
[صرخات] آه!
Gio?
جيو؟
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى قاتمة]
Here's the mouse.
وهنا الفأر.
Do you really have to show it to me?
هل لديك حقا لتظهر لي؟
I didn't know you were there.
لم أكن أعرف كنت هناك.
Wait! Where will you throw it?
انتظر! أين سترميها؟
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل الموسيقى]
Gio, where will you throw it?
جيو، أين سوف ترميها؟
No!
لا!
What do you mean by "No"?
ماذا تفعل يعني ب "لا"؟
They won't collect trash yet. It'll stink there.
لن يقوموا بجمع القمامة بعد. سوف نتن هناك.
[CLICKS TONGUE] Tsk.
[نقرات اللسان] تسك.
I told you not to throw it there.
قلت لك لا لرميها هناك.
Throw it outside the hotel premises.
رميها في الخارج مباني الفندق.
You're still acting bossy over this?
أنت لا تزال تتصرف متسلط على هذا؟
I think you forgot that I'm still the GM here, Gio.
أعتقد أنك نسيت أنني لا يزال المدير العام هنا، جيو.
You're still supervising me throwing the mouse?
أنت لا تزال تشرف علي رمي الماوس؟
- The mouse might escape! - What?
- قد يهرب الفأر! - ماذا؟
What do you mean? The mouse is dead!
ماذا تقصد؟ مات الفأر!
What's going on with you?
ماذا يحدث معك؟
Whatever, just throw it far away for the hotel's safety.
أيا كان، مجرد رميها بعيدا حفاظاً على سلامة الفندق.
- No! - [CLICKS TONGUE] Tsk.
- لا! - [نقرات اللسان] تسك.
You've always had that reaction about mice.
لقد كان لديك دائما رد الفعل هذا حول الفئران.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى حزينة]
- [LUNA] Gio, there's a mouse! - A  mouse?!
- [LUNA] جيو، هناك فأر! - فأر؟!
- Get it! Get it! - [MOUSE SQUEAKS]
- احصل عليه! احصل عليه! - [صرير الماوس]
It's right there! It's right there! Get it!
إنه هناك حق! إنه هناك! احصل عليه!
Hurry! Hurry!
على عجل! أسرع!
Go slowly, slowly!
تحرك ببطء، ببطء!
[SCREAMS] Gio! It ran away!
[صرخات] جيو! لقد هرب!
It ran... oh no, it got away! It's under the bed!
لقد ركض... أوه لا، لقد هرب! إنه تحت السرير!
- Where? - It's under the bed!
- أين؟ - إنه تحت السرير!
Wait, wait. You need to watch out for it.
انتظر، انتظر. عليك أن تنتبه لذلك.
- [MOUSE SQUEAKS] - [SCREAMS] Ah!
- [صرير الماوس] - [صراخ] آه!
There you go! Did you catch it?
ها أنت ذا! هل قبضت عليه؟
- Did you catch it? - Should I take a look?
- هل قبض عليه؟ - هل يجب أن ألقي نظرة؟
- Don't look! - How will I know?
- لا تنظر! - كيف سأعرف؟
It might escape! You should knock.
قد يهرب! يجب أن تطرق الباب.
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[صرير الماوس]
Slowly.
ببطء.
[KNOCKS]
[يقرع]
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[صرير الماوس]
- [KNOCKS] - Hmm?
- [يقرع] - همم؟
I think it's not moving anymore.
أعتقد أنها لم تعد تتحرك.
Maybe it's just there.
ربما يكون هناك فقط.
- I think that's fine. - Sure.
- أعتقد أن هذا جيد. - بالتأكيد.
[PANTING]
[لهث]
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[صرير الماوس]
[SCREAMS] Ah!
[صرخات] آه!
What's going on?! You're so noisy!
ماذا يحدث؟! أنت صاخب جدًا!
What's wrong with you both?!
ما خطبكما؟!
Grandma...
الجدة...
[LAUGHS]
[يضحك]
If this dead mouse comes back...
إذا كان هذا الفأر الميت يعود...
[PLASTIC RUSTLING]
[ سرقة البلاستيك ]
Hmm.
حسنًا.
You know, sometimes I think about
كما تعلمون، أفكر أحيانًا في
what I would do without you.
ماذا سأفعل بدونك.
Who'll chase away the mice in my life?
الذي سوف مطاردة بعيدا الفئران في حياتي؟
[SCOFFS] Don't think about that.
[سكوفس] لا تفكر في ذلك.
How could I not think about that?
كيف لا أستطيع ذلك أفكر في ذلك؟
They keep popping out of nowhere!
يستمرون في الظهور من العدم!
Because that won't happen.
لأن ذلك لن يحدث.
Gio.
جيو.
There are so many mice in Manila.
هناك الكثير من الفئران في مانيلا.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى حزينة]
That won't happen because I won't leave you.
وهذا لن يحدث لأنني لن أتركك.
["TADHANA" BY SOFRONIO VASQUEZ PLAYING]
["تادهانا" بقلم سوفرونيو فاسكيز يلعب]
["TADHANA" BY SOFRONIO VASQUEZ CONTINUES]
["تادهانا" بقلم سوفرونيو يستمر فاسكيز]
[PLASTIC RUSTLING]
[ سرقة البلاستيك ]
[CHESKA] Hey, stop frowning.
[تشيسكا] مهلا، توقف عن العبوس.
There's a guest coming.
هناك ضيف قادم.
We'll just accompany them, right?
سوف نرافق فقط لهم، أليس كذلك؟
My god... Justin please...
يا إلهي... جاستن من فضلك...
Keep in mind that you're still one of the owners.
ضع في اعتبارك أنك لا تزال كذلك أحد أصحابها.
Trixie and I are just siblings of the owners.
تريكسي وأنا مجرد أشقاء أصحابها.
Stop acting like that.
التوقف عن التصرف من هذا القبيل.
I'm doing this so I won't embarass Martin.
أنا أفعل هذا لذا لن أفعل إحراج مارتن.
My God!
يا إلاهي!
Let's just think of it as us helping our siblings.
دعونا نفكر في الأمر كما يلي لنا مساعدة إخواننا.
- Hey! Energy! Energy! - Ah!
- يا! طاقة! طاقة! - اه!
There's a guest!
هناك ضيف!
How will we attract guests?
كيف سنجذب الضيوف؟
Stand up! Jump around! That's it! Smile!
الوقوف! القفز حولها! هذا كل شيء! يبتسم!
[CHESKA] Energy!
[تشيسكا] الطاقة!
What's up with your faces? That's not exactly welcoming.
ما الأمر مع وجوهكم؟ هذا ليس ترحيبًا تمامًا.
- Pull yourselves together. - Let's go?
- اجمعوا أنفسكم معًا. - دعنا نذهب؟
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى هادئة]
You're just wearing that?
أنت فقط ترتدي ذلك؟
Umm... for island hopping?
أم... للتنقل بين الجزر؟
Who said we'll go island hopping?
ومن قال أننا سنذهب التنقل بين الجزيرة؟
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الهادئة]
Are we not?
هل نحن لا؟
- [JADE] Kiko. - Oh.
- [اليشم] كيكو. - أوه.
Have you been waiting long?
هل انتظرت طويلاً؟
Ah, not really.
اه، ليس حقا.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Oh, our amulet!
أوه، تميمة لدينا!
We need to wear it, hurry.
نحن بحاجة إلى لبسه، على عجل.
You did a good job with today's presentation, bud.
لقد قمت بعمل جيد مع عرض اليوم يا برعم.
Well, of course, I got it from you dad.
حسنا، بالطبع، لقد حصلت عليه منك أبي.
[ANDY] Let's get going.
[آندي] دعونا نذهب.
[ANDY] What's going on?
[آندي] ماذا يحدث؟
Is that Jade?
هل هذا اليشم؟
[ANDY] Jade?
[آندي] اليشم؟
Is that why you can't date her? She has a boyfriend?
هل هذا هو السبب في أنك لا تستطيع مواعدتها؟ لديها صديق؟
[CHUCKLES]
[ضحكة مكتومة]
- Let's go. - Mm-hmm.
- دعنا نذهب. - مم هم.
Wait, how do we get there?
انتظر، كيف نصل إلى هناك؟
Tricycle.
دراجة ثلاثية العجلات.
- Tricycle? - Yeah. Let's go.
- دراجة ثلاثية العجلات؟ - نعم. دعنا نذهب.
Okay, okay. Let's go.
حسنا، حسنا. دعنا نذهب.
Where are they going?
أين هم ذاهبون؟
[ANDY] Don't tell me you'll follow them?
[آندي] لا تخبرني سوف تتبعهم؟
- Dad, c'mon. Let's go. - What are you doing?
- أبي، هيا. دعنا نذهب. - ماذا تفعل؟
C'mon, just get in.
هيا، فقط ادخل.
- Grandpa! - Oh?
- الجد! - أوه؟
I also left your food inside the fridge.
لقد تركت طعامك أيضًا داخل الثلاجة.
Don't forget to take your medicine too.
لا تنسى أن تأخذ الدواء الخاص بك أيضا.
[BOTONG] What magazine?
[بوتونج] أي مجلة؟
I'm not reading a magazine.
أنا لا أقرأ مجلة.
I said medicine, Grandpa. The one you need to take.
قلت الطب يا جدي. الذي عليك أن تأخذه.
Ah...
اه...
Remember what I also told you, okay?
تذكر ماذا لقد أخبرتك أيضاً، حسناً؟
[BOTONG] Yes.
[بوتونج] نعم.
Do you even remember what I told you?
هل تتذكر حتى ماذا قلت لك؟
[BOTONG] Yeah, I know. I need to take my medicine.
[بوتونج] نعم، أعرف. أحتاج إلى تناول دوائي.
Not that! The ritual.
ليس هذا! الطقوس.
[BOTONG] What ritual?
[بوتونج] أية طقوس؟
The ritual that will prevent Sir Martin's date from happening
الطقوس التي ستمنع تاريخ السير مارتن من الحدوث
with whoever that woman is.
مع من تكون تلك المرأة.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
Okay, fine.
حسنًا، حسنًا.
- Promise, Grandpa? - Yes.
- وعد يا جدي؟ - نعم.
Oh!
أوه!
What is it this time?
ما هو هذه المرة؟
What?
ماذا؟
[AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل الموسيقى المحيطة]
Oh?
أوه؟
Is there a ritual that...
هل من طقوس...
will make me Sir Martin's date?
هل ستحدد لي موعداً مع السير مارتن؟
Take this, so you can have my DNA.
خذ هذا، حتى تتمكن لدي الحمض النووي الخاص بي.
Oh my goodness.
يا إلهي.
- Grandpa, please. - Mhm.
- الجد، من فضلك. - مم.
[BOTONG GRUMBLES]
[بوتونج تذمر]
[SARI] Please.
[ساري] من فضلك.
Okay, fine.
حسنًا، حسنًا.
- Thanks, Grandpa. - All right.
- شكرا يا جدي. - حسنًا.
[SARI] Ah!
[ساري] آه!
What is it this time?
ما هو هذه المرة؟
Buh-bye, Grandpa! I love you so much.
بوه وداعا، الجد! أنا أحبك جداً.
- Muah!
- مواه!
Bye, Grandpa! Don't forget to take your medicine, okay?
وداعا يا جدي! لا تنسى لتتناول دوائك، حسنًا؟
- Yes. Bye-bye! - Don't forget it! Buh-bye!
- نعم. وداعا وداعا! - لا تنساه! بوه وداعا!
- Bye, Grandpa! - Bye-bye!
- وداعا يا جدي! - وداعا وداعا!
[AMBIENT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى المحيطة]
Do you want to come here?
هل تريد المجيء إلى هنا؟
I can fetch you from there. Then you can stay here for now.
أستطيع أن أحضرك من هناك. ثم يمكنك البقاء هنا في الوقت الراهن.
Oh, don't bother!
أوه، لا تهتم!
I'll just distract you from your work.
أنا فقط سوف يصرف لك من عملك.
I'm already happy...
أنا سعيد بالفعل...
with you giving me a call.
مع أنك اتصلت بي.
Okay then.
حسنًا إذن.
But don't buy groceries for now, okay?
لكن لا تشتري البقالة في الوقت الراهن، حسنا؟
Let's just get whatever you need delivered there
دعونا فقط نحصل على أي شيء تحتاج تسليمها هناك
so you won't get too tired.
لذلك لن تتعب كثيرا.
Look at this boy.
انظر إلى هذا الصبي.
You wanted me to go on vacation there earlier,
أردت مني أن أذهب في إجازة هناك في وقت سابق،
but you're not letting me out now
لكنك لا تسمح لي خارج الآن
because you don't want me to go to the wet market.
لأنك لا تريدني للذهاب إلى السوق الرطبة.
What do you want me to do here?
ماذا تريد مني أن أفعل هنا؟
Luna? Is that Luna?
لونا؟ هل هذه لونا؟
- Luna! Luna! - Grandma, stop.
- لونا! لونا! - جدتي، توقفي.
- Luna, is that you? - Grandma, stop!
- لونا، هل هذه أنت؟ - جدتي، توقفي!
Grandma, don't call her.
الجدة، لا تتصل بها.
[GIO'S GRANDMA] She looks so beautiful! Is that you, Luna?
[جدة جيو] إنها تبدو جميل جدًا! هل هذه أنت يا لونا؟
Hello, Grandma.
مرحبا الجدة.
Yes, this is Luna.
نعم، هذه لونا.
[GIO'S GRANDMA] Oh, Luna! You're still beautiful and sexy.
[جدة جيو] أوه، لونا! مازلت جميلة ومثيرة.
How are you doing?
كيف حالك؟
I'm doing okay.
أنا بخير.
How about you? How's your blood pressure?
ماذا عنك؟ كيف هو ضغط دمك؟
[GIO'S GRANDMA] Well, it's still high.
[جدة جيو] حسنًا، لا يزال السعر مرتفعًا.
But you know, whenever I see someone pretty, it goes down.
ولكن كما تعلمون، كلما رأيت شخص جميل، فإنه ينخفض.
Oh my!
يا بلدي!
You haven't changed. You still joke a lot.
أنت لم تتغير. لا تزال تمزح كثيرا.
Take care of your health, okay?
اعتني بصحتك، حسنًا؟
Getting sick nowadays is really hard.
الإصابة بالمرض في أيامنا هذه من الصعب حقا.
[GIO'S GRANDMA] Thank you, dear.
[جدة جيو] شكرًا لك، عزيزتي.
There's a lot of you who always remind me about it.
هناك الكثير منكم ذكرني به دائمًا.
Is laing still your favorite?
هل لا يزال laing هو المفضل لديك؟
Your laing is my only favorite.
لينغ الخاص بك هو مفضلتي الوحيدة.
[GIO'S GRANDMA SQUEALS] Okay then.
[صرخات جدة جيو] حسنًا إذن.
I'll have some sent to you there.
سأرسل بعض لك هناك.
Remind Gio that I'll send you some, okay?
ذكّر جيو بذلك سأرسل لك البعض، حسنًا؟
Okay then, Grandma.
حسنًا إذن يا جدتي.
I'll get going to take care of some stuff.
سأذهب لرعاية من بعض الاشياء.
Oh?
أوه؟
Do you work in the hotel as well?
هل تعمل في الفندق كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Okay then.
حسنًا إذن.
Bye-bye, Grandma. Take care.
وداعا يا جدتي. يعتني.
- Bye-bye, Grandma. - You too, dear.
- وداعا يا جدتي. - وأنت أيضًا يا عزيزي.
Always take care, okay?
كن حذرا دائما، حسنا؟
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى هادئة]
Hey!
مرحبًا!
You're so naughty.
أنت شقي جدًا.
You didn't even tell me that Luna was there.
أنت لم تخبرني حتى أن لونا كانت هناك.
It doesn't matter, Grandma.
لا يهم يا جدتي.
How could it not?
وكيف لا؟
She's the only woman you brought to our house.
إنها المرأة الوحيدة أحضرته إلى منزلنا.
I miss you, Grandma!
اشتقت لك يا جدتي!
I miss you so much!
أفتقدك كثيرًا!
Hmm! There you go again!
همم! ها أنت ذا مرة أخرى!
There you go again!
ها أنت ذا مرة أخرى!
But when you're ready, tell me the story, okay?
ولكن عندما تكون مستعدًا، أخبرني القصة، حسنا؟
I love you, my grandson. I miss you too!
أنا أحبك، حفيدي. وأنا أفتقدك أيضًا!
Muah!
مواه!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الناعمة]
[SARI] I'm sorry, sir!
[ساري] أنا آسف يا سيدي!
You know there is a lot to do at the hotel.
أنت تعلم أن هناك الكثير للقيام به في الفندق.
The meeting with Gerard's dad is already tomorrow.
اللقاء مع والد جيرارد هو بالفعل غدا.
- Then you're late?! - I'll just extend, sir!
- إذن تأخرت؟! - سأمتد فقط، يا سيدي!
I'll work overtime for free!
سأعمل وقتًا إضافيًا مجانًا!
- Wait, about Gerard's dad-- - [SHUSHES]
- انتظر، بشأن والد جيرارد-- - [يسكت]
Quiet.
هادئ.
Why are you shushing me?
لماذا تسكتني؟
Because this is a personal meeting.
لأن هذا أمر شخصي اجتماع.
Sari, promise me you won't tell anyone else.
ساري، وعد مني لن أقول لأي شخص آخر.
[MARTIN SIGHS DEEPLY]
[مارتن يتنهد بعمق]
Does that mean you have a date already?
هل هذا يعني لديك موعد بالفعل؟
You don't have to worry about that.
ليس عليك أن تفعل ذلك تقلق بشأن ذلك.
I need the venue. I need food.
أحتاج المكان. انا بحاجة للطعام.
- And I need flowers. - You know, sir, you're right!
- وأنا بحاجة إلى الزهور. - كما تعلم يا سيدي، أنت على حق!
[SHUSHES]
[يصمت]
You don't have to worry about the date.
لا داعي للقلق حول التاريخ.
You can prove to Mr. Ronald that
يمكنك أن تثبت للسيد رونالد أن
you're a good businessman even if you don't have a date.
أنت رجل أعمال جيد حتى إذا لم يكن لديك موعد.
If he finds out that you're the perfect example
إذا اكتشف أنك المثال المثالى
of a businessman who's TDH!
لرجل أعمال TDH!
Don't tell me it's tall--
لا تقل لي أنه طويل--
T, for thoughtful.
T، للتفكير.
You always pay attention to details and people, sir.
أنت دائما تولي اهتماما إلى التفاصيل والناس، يا سيدي.
And D, for driven.
و D للمدفوعة.
You will attack when needed to, sir!
سوف تهاجم عندما اللازمة يا سيدي!
And H, for hands-on.
و H للتدريب العملي.
You're always present and involved.
أنت حاضر دائمًا ومتورطة.
- That's you, sir! TDH! - [MARTIN] Raphie!
- هذا أنت يا سيدي! TDH! - [مارتن] رافي!
Sir! Sir! Sir!
سيد! سيد! سيد!
Edward, are you serious?
إدوارد، هل أنت جاد؟
We even left the car far away.
حتى أننا غادرنا السيارة بعيدة.
Dad, they can't see us.
أبي، لا يمكنهم رؤيتنا.
- Hide a bit more. - [SCOFFS]
- إخفاء أكثر قليلا. - [سخرية]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى مرحة]
Remind me again, why are we doing this?
ذكرني مرة أخرى، لماذا نفعل هذا؟
I'm not even prepared!
أنا لست مستعدًا حتى!
Look, I'm wearing leather shoes.
أنظر، أنا أرتدي حذاء جلدي.
I'm sorry, Dad, okay?
أنا آسف يا أبي، حسنًا؟
After the breakfast tomorrow, we will climb the mountain.
بعد الإفطار غدا سوف نتسلق الجبل.
The hut you'll sleep in has been prepared already.
الكوخ الذي ستنام فيه تم إعداده بالفعل.
You'll be fine sleeping next to each other, right?
سوف تكون بخير النوم بجانب بعضها البعض، أليس كذلك؟
You're a couple anyway.
أنتم زوجين على أي حال.
[EXCLAIMS]
[يصرخ]
This guy? My boyfriend?
هذا الرجل؟ صديقي؟
H-he's not.
ح-إنه ليس كذلك.
[CHUCKLES]
[ضحكة مكتومة]
Oh no, I'm sorry.
أوه لا، أنا آسف.
I thought you were a couple.
اعتقدت أنك كنت زوجين.
What a waste. You look good together.
يا لها من مضيعة. تبدو جيدة معا.
Ah, her?
اه، لها؟
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY] She's just my friend.
[ضحكة خافتة بعصبية] إنها مجرد صديقتي.
Just so you know,
فقط لعلمك،
we've been friends since we were kids.
لقد كنا أصدقاء منذ أن كنا أطفالا.
Oh, how adorable.
أوه، كم هو رائعتين.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى متأمل]
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[حفيف الأوراق]
[EDWARD] Dad, hide!
[إدوارد] أبي، اختبئ!
Dad!
أب!
[LAUGHS]
[يضحك]
Dad, they might hear us. Be quiet!
أبي، ربما يسمعوننا. كن هادئاً!
I can't help it, it's funny.
لا أستطيع مساعدته، إنه مضحك.
Jade.
يشم.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى هادئة]
Jade.
يشم.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Huh?
هاه؟
[STUTTERING] Oh, it's nothing.
[تلعثم] أوه، إنه لا شيء.
I just thought I had seen...
لقد ظننت أنني رأيت...
Who?
من؟
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الناعمة]
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
Okay, we'll go to the hut then.
حسنًا، سنذهب إلى الكوخ إذن.
- It's this way. - Ah, let's get going.
- إنها بهذه الطريقة. - آه، دعونا نذهب.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الناعمة]
[EDWARD] You know what, Dad?
[إدوارد] هل تعرف ماذا يا أبي؟
Leave this to me.
اترك هذا لي.
I'll handle it myself, so just go home.
سأتولى الأمر بنفسي، لذلك فقط اذهب إلى المنزل.
[ANDY] Why should I go home?
[أندي] لماذا يجب أن أعود إلى المنزل؟
You brought me here then you'd tell me to go home?
لقد أحضرتني إلى هنا إذن هل ستخبرني أن أذهب للمنزل؟
No, no, no. I'm staying right here.
لا، لا، لا. أنا باق هنا.
I want to see why you're acting like that.
أريد أن أرى السبب أنت تتصرف بهذه الطريقة.
And besides, this is free entertainment.
وإلى جانب ذلك، هذا ترفيه مجاني.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى الناعمة]
[MARTIN SIGHS] Finally!
[تنهدات مارتن] أخيرًا!
Pearl said yes?
قالت بيرل نعم؟
Yes, I'm not that close with Pearl.
نعم، أنا لست كذلك التي تغلق مع بيرل.
But as soon as I mentioned your name,
ولكن بمجرد أن ذكرت اسمك
she immediately said yes.
قالت نعم على الفور.
[EXHALES DEEPLY] You're such a lifesaver, Trixie.
[يزفر بعمق] أنت مثل المنقذ، تريكسي.
Do you know that?
هل تعرف ذلك؟
Thank you, Trixie.
شكرا تريكسي.
[TRIXIE] But she said she had no dress to wear.
[TRIXIE] لكنها قالت لم يكن لديها فستان ترتديه.
You know, because it's last minute.
كما تعلمون، لأنها اللحظة الأخيرة.
So, I put in your car
لذلك، وضعت في سيارتك
the dress that I was going to lend to her.
اللباس الذي كنت ذاهبا لإقراضها.
I had to do that because, of course,
كان علي أن أفعل ذلك لأنه، بالطبع
I don't know how long I'll be staying here.
لا أعرف كم من الوقت سأبقى هنا.
[MARTIN SIGHS] I don't know what I'd do without you.
[تنهدات مارتن] لا أعرف ماذا سأفعل بدونك.
You even accompanied a guest on a tour, didn't you?
حتى أنك رافقت ضيفًا في جولة، أليس كذلك؟
I'm doing this for you, brother.
أنا أفعل هذا من أجلك يا أخي.
[MARTIN] I'll make it up to you, okay?
[مارتن] سأفعل ذلك متروك لك، حسنا؟
All right. Thanks. Bye. Love you.
حسنًا. شكرًا. الوداع. أحبك.
- Take care. - Love you.
- اعتني بنفسك. - أحبك.
Buh-bye.
بوه وداعا.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[صفير الهاتف]
Hey!
يا!
You won't wait for me, really?
لن تنتظريني، حقاً؟
[MARTIN] This is Pearl's number.
[مارتن] هذا هو رقم بيرل.
Call her and ask what time she needs to be picked up.
اتصل بها واسألها متى؟ يجب أن يتم اصطحابها.
Okay.
تمام.
[PHONE CLICKS]
[نقرات الهاتف]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى متأمل]
Pearl Lim.
بيرل ليم.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[نقرات اللسان]
Huh?
هاه؟
She looks like she's just ahead of me
انها تبدو وكأنها إنها أمامي
because she's better in English.
لأنها أفضل في اللغة الإنجليزية.
But we're just equal in looks!
لكننا متساوون في المظهر!
[TRIXIE] Hey!
[تريكسي] مهلا!
Wait for me!
الانتظار لي!
[COUGHS]
[السعال]
Hey, wait for me!
مهلا، انتظرني!
Francheska.
فرانشيسكا.
Go wait for her.
اذهب وانتظرها.
Let's go ahead, Maria.
دعنا نمضي قدما، ماريا.
[TRIXIE PANTING]
[تريكسي يلهث]
Hey.
يا.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Are you in bad terms?
هل أنت في حالة سيئة؟
[TRIXIE SCOFFS]
[تريكسي يسخر]
Look at this woman. I was talking to you.
انظر إلى هذه المرأة. كنت أتحدث معك.
I'll bang your heads to each other, you'll see.
سأضرب رؤوسكم لبعضهم البعض، سترى.
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل الموسيقى الحماسية]
Okay.
تمام.
This way.
من هنا.
[JUSTIN SIGHS]
[يتنهد جاستن]
How moody. We should just be enjoying this.
كيف متقلب المزاج. يجب أن نستمتع بهذا فقط.
Do you even know where we're going?
هل تعرف حتى إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
[TRIXIE] Nope.
[تريكسي] كلا.
Then why are you all leading the way?
ثم لماذا أنتم جميعا تقود الطريق؟
You know, we should put more of this...
كما تعلمون، ينبغي لنا ضع المزيد من هذا...
[MAN] It's beautiful here.
[رجل] المكان جميل هنا.
around the hotel.
حول الفندق.
Solenn?
سولين؟
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYS]
[مسرحيات موسيقية متأملة]
Solenn.
سولين.
- Solenn! - Cha-Chase?
- سولين! - تشا تشيس؟
Oh my god!
يا إلهي!
[CHUCKLES] Wow!
[ضحكة مكتومة] واو!
I missed you!
أفتقدك!
I can't believe it.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق ذلك.
We haven't seen each other in a long time.
لم نر بعضهما البعض لفترة طويلة.
How have you been?
كيف كان حالك؟
It's been what?
لقد كان ماذا؟
It's been a few years, right?
لقد مرت بضع سنوات، أليس كذلك؟
[LUNA] What are you doing here?
[لونا] ماذا تفعل هنا؟
[CHASE] Well...
[تشيس] حسنًا...
You haven't come back in Manila for a long time.
أنت لم تعود في مانيلا لفترة طويلة.
Wait a second, when did you last come to the bar?
انتظر لحظة، متى حدث ذلك آخر مرة أتيت إلى الحانة؟
It's been a while.
لقد مضى وقت طويل.
How long has it been?
كم من الوقت مضى؟
Wow, you know what?
واو، هل تعرف ماذا؟
I used to always ask Peter where you were.
كنت دائما أسأل بيتر أين كنت.
You didn't even reply to me.
أنت لم ترد حتى علي.
All the while, you were just here.
طوال الوقت، كنت هنا للتو.
You know, Peter and I still hang out to this day.
كما تعلمون، بيتر وأنا لا نزال شنق حتى يومنا هذا.
There's this new bar in QC.
هناك هذا الشريط الجديد في مراقبة الجودة.
You know, we're still the same.
كما تعلمون، نحن لا نزال كما هو.
You know how that man is.
أنت تعرف كيف هو هذا الرجل.
Do you guys still talk?
هل مازلتم تتحدثون يا رفاق؟
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى موروس]
Reservation! Do you have a reservation already?
حجز! هل لديك حجز بالفعل؟
- Hey, is there a "Chase" there? - Here, here!
- مهلا، هل هناك "تشيس" هناك؟ - هنا، هنا!
Why don't you seem to have any trust in me?
لماذا لا يبدو أن لديك أي ثقة في؟
You know, there's no vacancy at my friends' hotel anymore.
كما تعلمون، ليس هناك منصب شاغر في فندق أصدقائي بعد الآن.
That's why I came here instead.
ولهذا السبب جئت إلى هنا بدلا من ذلك.
If only I had known you were working here,
لو كنت أعرف فقط كنت تعمل هنا،
we would've all booked here instead.
كنا جميعا حجزت هنا بدلا من ذلك.
You know, I missed you and Peter so much.
كما تعلمون، اشتقت لك وبطرس كثيرا.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر موسيقى موروس]
[CHASE] Our night-out parties were wild, weren't they?
[مطاردة] حفلاتنا الليلية كانوا متوحشين، أليس كذلك؟
I missed our dance moves like this one.
لقد فاتني حركات رقصنا مثل هذا.
Those parties were so fun!
كانت تلك الحفلات ممتعة للغاية!
Didn't you even miss that?
لم تفوت حتى ذلك؟
It's good to see you, Chase.
من الجيد رؤيتك يا تشيس.
That quickly?
بهذه السرعة؟
I missed you!
أفتقدك!
You know, I missed you so much.
كما تعلمون، لقد اشتقت لك كثيرا.
I hope we could party together again.
آمل أن نتمكن من الاحتفال معا مرة أخرى.
Later.
لاحقاً.
Let's see each other, okay?
دعونا نرى بعضنا البعض، حسنا؟
Yes, okay.
نعم حسنا.
Let's party later, okay?
دعنا نحتفل لاحقاً، حسناً؟
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر موسيقى موروس]
- Please sign here, sir. - Which one?
- من فضلك وقع هنا يا سيدي. - أيها؟
[DOOR OPENS]
[يفتح الباب]
[DOOR THUDS]
[طرقات الباب]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[التنفس بشدة]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر موسيقى موروس]
With so many hotels out there,
مع وجود العديد من الفنادق هناك،
why is Peter's friend here?
لماذا صديق بيتر هنا؟
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر موسيقى موروس]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل موسيقى متأمل]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[طرق الباب]
Sir, we're closed today.
سيدي، نحن مغلقون اليوم.
Ma'am, please. I just need to ask something.
سيدتي، من فضلك. أنا فقط بحاجة إلى أن أسأل شيئا.
We're closed, sir.
نحن مغلقون يا سيدي.
- [KNOCKING CONTINUES] - Please, ma'am.
- [يستمر الطرق] - من فضلك سيدتي.
Can you open the door?
هل يمكنك فتح الباب؟
[KEYS CLICKING]
[النقر على المفاتيح]
[DOOR LOCK CLICKS]
[نقرات قفل الباب]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى المتأملة]
Ma'am, uh... I just want to know
سيدتي اه... أريد فقط أن أعرف
who sent the package to Michael Fernandez
الذي أرسل الحزمة إلى مايكل فرنانديز
during Holy Week.
خلال أسبوع الآلام.
Uh, go ahead, just take it to storage.
اه، تفضل، فقط خذها للتخزين.
Okay, ma'am.
حسنا سيدتي.
But Mr. Almazan, the sender is confidential
لكن السيد المازان، المرسل سري
unless the receiver is the one asking.
إلا إذا كان المتلقي هو الذي يسأل.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى المتأملة]
Uh, ma'am, you don't need to print it.
اه سيدتي لا تحتاج إلى طباعته.
Just type it here on my phone.
فقط اكتبه هنا على هاتفي.
So it can't be traced back to you.
لذلك لا يمكن تتبعه العودة إليك.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[تستمر الموسيقى المتأملة]
[KEYBOARD CLINKING]
[طقطقة لوحة المفاتيح]
"Vito Arsenia #107 Victor Drive, Puerto Felicia"
"فيتو أرسينيا #107 فيكتور درايف، بويرتو فيليسيا"
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING] - [CROW CAWING]
- [تشغيل موسيقى غريب] - [نعيق الغراب]
[CROW CAWING]
[نعيق الغراب]
[MAN] Who are you?
[رجل] من أنت؟
Vito Arsenia?
فيتو أرسينيا؟
Leon Almazan.
ليون المازان.
Are you Vito?
هل أنت فيتو؟
What do you need?
ماذا تحتاج؟
You sent documents to Michael Fernandez
لقد أرسلت المستندات إلى مايكل فرنانديز
before he died.
قبل وفاته.
Do you remember?
هل تذكر؟
You're Federico Almazan's son?
هل أنت ابن فيديريكو ألمازان؟
Come in.
ادخل.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[تشغيل الموسيقى المثيرة]
Is this some kind of sun dance?
هل هذا نوع من رقصة الشمس؟
We dance up here and our bad luck disappears?
نحن نرقص هنا و حظنا السيئ يختفي؟
That's what he said.
هذا ما قاله.
I just really can't leave Jade with that guy.
أنا حقًا لا أستطيع ترك جايد مع ذلك الرجل.
Every time they're together, something bad happens.
في كل مرة يكونان معًا، يحدث شيء سيء.
Well, Pearl's not coming.
حسنًا، بيرل لن يأتي.
So I need a new date.
إذن أنا بحاجة إلى تاريخ جديد.
Just admit it, you want you guys to be the only ones
فقط أعترف بذلك، كما تريد أنتم يا رفاق أن تكونوا الوحيدين
with the upper hand here in the hotel!
باليد العليا هنا في الفندق!
[SCOFFS] All you do is keep attacking.
[سكوفس] كل ما تفعله هو الاستمرار في الهجوم.
Paying off the bank loan is urgent!
سداد القرض البنكي أمر عاجل!
We are going to invest in Hotel 88.
نحن نذهب للاستثمار في فندق 88.
Invest?
استثمر؟
Partner?
شريك؟
Leon, he's so quiet, right?
ليون، إنه هادئ جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
But from what I can see,
لكن مما أستطيع رؤيته،
he's the one with the most secrets.
إنه الشخص بأكثر الأسرار.
What do you have to do with Sandro?
ماذا عليك أن تفعل مع ساندرو؟
Don't you ever mention that name in this house again!
لا تذكر من أي وقت مضى هذا الاسم في هذا المنزل مرة أخرى!
You!
أنت!
There's a shadow following you.
هناك ظل يتبعك.
There are dangers waiting for you.
هناك مخاطر في انتظاركم.
[BLOW LANDS]
[الأراضي المنفجرة]